<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Journal of Nixfreak - Blog Category</title><link href="https://nixfreak.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://nixfreak.github.io/feeds/blog-category.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://nixfreak.github.io/</id><updated>2020-08-25T09:57:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>Goal Setting</title><link href="https://nixfreak.github.io/first-journal-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-08-25T09:57:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-25T09:57:00-05:00</updated><author><name>NiX</name></author><id>tag:nixfreak.github.io,2020-08-25:/first-journal-post.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a test for a first blog for journal&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;First blog published ever&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well after years and years of not actually using a blog, I have finally did it. 
Anyway this site will be dedicated to #security e.g. hacking, physical securiy, CTFs and more. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;I want to forcus on seperate categories for all of this eventually.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little about me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am 0x28 years old, I have been in Information Security over a decade now. I basically taght myself computer security, reverse engineering and so on. I use #blackarch as my security distro because I am an #Archlinux user and have been since it was in beta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goal setting is my topic because I want to get better at security. So I decided to quick screwing around and dig down deep into hacking, information security, reverse engineering, and exploit writing. Since I am 0x28 I woulike to think that its never to late to teach an old dog new tricks. I don't like using metasploit for learning and the reason is, is because you really don't learn a thing when you pop! a box and reverse shell using meterpreter. I am here to learn very detail security and OS properties. I started this blog for myself so I could hae a log of everything I am learning. I use JoplinApp for all my notes but I think its time to start a blog so I can actually show it and so I can view it easily online when needed. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog Category"></category></entry></feed>